我生了俩孩子  要给老公吹箫
I spit out two kids, blew my husband,
还得看着这个鬼地方
and taking care of this shithole.
我都能抽出时间看《无耻家庭》
I still had time to watch Shameless.
你他妈有什么借口
What's your damn excuse?
两块钱
$2.
瞧见了吗
Did you see that?
都他妈一帮穷鬼
These cheap motherfuckers.
我要告诉在座的诸位
I just want everybody here
我他妈是同性恋
to know I'm fucking gay.
我要宰了你
I'll fucking kill you!
你真的出柜了
So you really came out, huh?
不代表我要开始
It doesn't mean I'm gonna wear
穿裙子或什么的
a fucking dress or anything.
你他妈怎么回事
What the fuck's going on with you?
刚才还像个超人一样
One minute you're like superman,
到处跑  还做煎饼
running around making pancakes,
拍什么日出的鬼照片
taking pictures of the goddamn sunrise.
一回头你就要割别人的喉咙
And the next thing, you want to cut somebody's throat.
我不禁注意到这张日程表
I couldn't help but notice the, uh, schedule.
我同步到你的新手机里了
I synced it to your new phone.
这张日程表  不是我的风格
The schedule, it's just-- it's--it's not me.
那结果怎样呢
How's that working out for you?
帮我拿糖果
Just help me grab some candy.
我家住这里
My family lives in there.
住超市里吗
The supermarket?
住在货车里面
In the van.
全校七八年级的人都在笑话我
I'm the laughing stock of the 7th and 8th grade.
我还以为他喜欢我
I thought he liked me.
他邀我当舞伴
He asked me to the dance.
我带你去舞会吧
I'll take you to the dance.
你们好啊
Well, hello.
那些可爱的矮子
Those adorable children.
我和罗杰本来都要结婚
Roger and I, we were gonna get married
然后收养他们了  结果他露出了真面目
and adopt them before he showed his true colors.
我只需要一纸婚书
All I need is a marriage certificate.
弗朗西斯·加拉格  你愿意娶我吗
Francis Gallagher, will you marry me?
在此  我宣布  你们成为合法夫妻
It is my honor to declare you man and wife.
你可以亲吻新郎了
You may kiss the groom.
他情况危急
He's in serious condition,
所以我们把他挪到名单第一位了
so they moved him up the waiting list.
那是什么意思
What does that mean?
-他要得到一个新肝了  -我这是在哪儿  黛比
- He's getting a liver. - Where am I, Debbie?
我是萨咪
I'm Sammi.
我最好去叫医生
I better get the doctor.
妈妈是要去哪儿  利普
Where's mama going, Lip?
老兄  你这是怎么了  我是卡尔
Dude, what's wrong with you? I'm Carl.
加拉格先生出现了
Mr. Gallagher is suffering
术后谵妄的症状
from postoperative delirium.
妈  别这样  大庭广众的
Mm, mom, stop. We're in public.
等我们回家再继续
Wait till we get home.
我不是你的朋友
I'm not your friend.
我是来确保你没有违反
I'm here to make sure you don't violate
你的假释条件
the terms of your probation.
菲奥娜没有回家
Fiona never came home.
她违反了假释条例
She violated probation.
我们这是要去哪儿
Where are we going?
看起来像是要去迪凯特惩教署
Looks like Decatur Correctional.
排成一队下车
Off the bus. Single line.
别说话  别挤
No talking, no pushing.
无耻家庭
第四季第十二集
■
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
翻译：  扎克不渣      重案组李Sir      拉图      君君
■
翻译：  姚小事     爱卿遛小鸟     猛回头     Greentie
时间轴：  芝麻圆子       浓子       Jessie
■
校对：  Greentie      落
后期： 孤帆          总监： 落
■
爸
Dad?
你感觉怎么样
How are you feeling?
这玩意儿输的是吗啡吗
Does this thing dispense morphine?
你很疼吗
Are you in pain?
是的
Yes.
非常疼的那种
A lot of pain?
没错  老天
Yes. Jesus.
老爸
Daddy.
你知道我是谁吗
Do you know who I am?
什么
What?
我是谁
Who am I?
萨咪
Sammi.
早上好啊  早起的鸟儿先生
Good morning, Mr. Early Bird.
我的家人在哪里
Where--where's my family?
-我就在这里  爸  -我们都在这里  亲爱的
- I'm right here, dad. - We're here, honey.
看来以前的老爸回来了
I think dad's back.
要不然我还能在哪里呢
Where the hell else would I be?
你知道你在哪里吗
Do you know where you are?
医院
A hospital?
哪里的医院
A hospital where?
芝加哥的啊  老天
Chicago. Jesus.
你们两个白痴这是发什么神经呢
What the hell is wrong with you two idiots?
我去叫护士过来
I'll go get the nurse.
弗兰克
Oh, Frank.
是你  你终于清醒了
It's you. You're back!
-我就知道你会清醒过来的  -老天
- I knew you'd be back. - Oh, jesus.
加拉格女士  我跟你说过不要靠床太近
Mrs. Gallagher, I told you to stay off the bed.
你会把他身上的缝合钉都扯开的
You're gonna rip out his staples.
加拉格女士
Mrs. Gallagher?
看来他是真的清醒了
I don't think he's confused anymore.
加拉格女士  我们结婚了
Mrs. Gallagher? We're married?
貌似还是有点小迷糊
Still sounds pretty confused to me.
-什么时候的事  -亲爱的
- Since when? - Oh, honey.
你这是逗我玩呢
You're a hoot.
我想他肯定很疼
I think he's in pain.
你感觉很疼吗  加拉格先生
You in pain, Mr. Gallagher?
是的  是的  都快疼死我了
Yes. Yes, excruciating.
这里有什么药
What do we got going here?
度冷丁  维柯丁
Demerol? Vicodin?
要不给我来点儿二氢吗啡酮[均为止痛药]
What say we toss in dilaudid,
好让老子舒坦点儿
try to take the edge off of this bitch?
疼痛是福报  加拉格先生
Pain is a blessing, Mr. Gallagher,
是天主治愈你的过程中的一部分
part of the good lord's healing process.
我去给你拿早餐过来
I'ma go get your breakfast.
我真高兴你清醒过来了  爸
I'm so glad you're back, dad.
我们结婚了
We're married?
是不是很美好啊
Isn't it wonderful?
我去给加里打个电话
I'm gonna go call Gary,
叫他把孩子们都带过来
and have him bring the kids down.
加里是他妈谁
Who the hell's Gary?
是你刚得的印第安裔孩子中的一个
One of your new native american kids.
应该是留贾斯丁·比伯发型的那个
I think he's the one with the Justin Bieber haircut.
我还有印第安裔的孩子了
I have native american kids?
有五个呢
Five.
真他妈冷死了  暖气出问题了吗
It's fucking freezing. What's up with the heat?
菲奥娜让我们晚上就关掉  节约天然气
Fiona has us turning it down at night, save on gas.
老天  我几乎能看到自己的呼吸了
Christ. I can almost see my breath.
没错  你很快就能看到了
Yeah, you will be able to soon.
天然气公司周五就要给咱们停了
Gas company's cutting us off on Friday.
什么  菲奥娜没交钱吗
What, Fiona didn't pay it?
她交了她付得起的那部分了
She paid what she could.
好吧  我从阿曼达父母那里
All right, well, I got some money
弄到了些钱
from Amanda's folks.
列个清单  看看咱们有哪些费要交
Make a list. We'll pay some bills, yeah?
阿曼达要留下来
Amanda's staying?
怎么  你不喜欢她
Why, you don't like her?
只要她能帮我们付账单
I like her as long as she's helping us
我就喜欢
pay some bills.
起床  上学了
Yo, up. School.
我们怎么处理他
What are we supposed to do with him?
我们可以把他送到
We could drop him off at the butcher
廉价超市的屠夫那里
over at the Food 4 Less,
看看他们能不能把他剁了当培根
see if they'll chop him up for bacon.
我们早餐吃培根吗
We having bacon for breakfast?
不  我们吃恰奇
Nah, we're eating Chuckie.
酷
Oh, cool.
她现在跟你一起睡了
She's sleeping with you now?
你女朋友就跟你一起睡
Your girlfriend sleeps with you.
是的  阿曼达20岁了  不是12岁
Yeah, Amanda's 20, not 12.
邦妮13岁了
Bonnie's 13.
我还是不想让她跟你一起睡
I still don't want her sleeping with you.
她不想做爱
She doesn't want to have sex,
因为她妈妈以前的男朋友
something about her mom's old boyfriend
还有摩托车黑帮什么的
and a biker gang.
-有咖啡吗  -有  给你
- Coffee? - Oh, yeah, here.
-谢了  -都是未付的票据
- Thanks. - Outstanding bills.
天呐  电费跟租金也逾期了
Jesus. What, electric and rent are late too?
好了  你能去一下支票现金兑换所吗
All right, can you get to the check-cashing place?
今天买点汇票回来
Buy some money orders today?
好的
Yeah, absolutely.
如果都要还清的话可能需要1900块
More like 1,900 if you want to pay everything off.
好了  给你
All right. There you go.
藏在靴子里什么的  好吗
Hide it in your boot or something, okay?
没人敢抢我
Nobody's gonna roll me.
我都带着防狼喷雾跟剃刀
I carry pepper spray and a shiv.
发钱了吗
Handing out money?
邦妮的弟弟们需要吃点消炎药
Bonnie's brothers need a few z-paks
还要买几瓶除虱洗发水
and a couple bottles of rid.
邦妮的流浪孩子们还要
You know, how much longer are Bonnie's
在咱们家客厅住多久
lost boys gonna be sacked out in the living room?
你说他们可以住在这
You said they could stay here.
是的  只是一晚
Yeah, for one night.
让他们睡路边
All right, kick 'em to the curb,
这里不是孤儿院
this isn't an orphanage.
我们什么时候去看菲奥娜
When are we gonna go visit Fiona?
要三个小时车程
It's three hours away.
每条路都是
Each way.
我们要怎么去那里
How the hell are we supposed to get down there?
-坐公交  -管你女朋友借车
- Bus. - Borrow your girlfriend's car.
我还有物理实验没有做完
No, look. I'm behind on a physics lab.
我还有几轮兼职要补上
I've got work-study shifts to make up
还要交文学课的论文
and a paper due in lit.
好吧  这个周末去
Okay, this weekend.
要了命了
You know, jesus, guys.
是在乡村俱乐部监狱过90天
It's 90 days in country club jail.
好吗  不是关塔那摩监狱
All right, it's not guantanamo.
她有可能学了一门手艺
Okay, she's probably learning a useful trade,
补了补西班牙语
brushing up on her spanish.
解散
Clear.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
不是我生日
It's not my birthday.
那我也送你个礼物
I got you a little present anyway.
能让今天轻松一些
Make the day go easy.
快点
Come on, guys.
卡尔
Yo, Carl.
我们也带他们上学吗
We taking all them to school too?
不是  送他们回以前住的停车场
No, back to the parking lot where they live.
什么  他们住在停车场
What, they live in a parking lot?
货车里  但是在停车场
Van, but it's in a parking lot.
恰奇怎么办
What are we gonna do with Chuckie?
我得把他带回医院
I have to take him back to the hospital
去见他妈妈和弗兰克
to see his mom and Frank.
我们坐不下
We're not all gonna fit.
当然能了
Sure we will.
你有西服吗
Do you own a suit?
西服
A suit?
最好是黑色
Preferably black.
为什么  我们要去参加葬礼吗
Why, are we going to a funeral?
更惨  我姐妹会的徽章授予典礼
Worse--pinning ceremony at my sorority.
-什么  -就那些
- What? - You know,
白裙子  唱歌  还有蜡烛
white dresses, chanting, candles.
你有没有西服
Do you own a suit or not?
不  没有
Uh, no. No, not.
那得赶紧给你弄一套
Well, then I guess we better get you one.
你现在是出柜的高调基佬了是吧
So you are rainbow boy now?
你把头发怎么了
The fuck you do to your hair?
你要开始穿粉色毛衣
You wear pink sweaters and
喷男士香水了吗
stink of man perfume now?
我穿粉色不好看
I look shitty in pink.
我操
What the fuck?
你喜欢鸡巴  是吧
You like the penis, yes?
正上方就是一对奶子  谁喜欢
Not when there's tits directly above it.
你想要它插进你拉屎的洞吗
You want it up in your poop place?
不想  你他妈赶紧...
No, I don't-- I want you--fucking--
赶紧给我收起来
I want you to put it away.
能收起来吗
Can you put that away?
把那东西收起来  求你了
Put that fucking thing away, please.
谢谢
Thank you.
你爱他
You love him?
可能吧
Maybe.
我不知道
I don't know.
因为他有个真的鸡巴
Because he has a real penis?
我猜是吧
Yeah, I guess.
我讨厌鸡巴
I hate the penis.
丑陋至极的肉棒子
Ugly fucking skin stick.
见着洞就想往里插
Always trying to get in where it doesn't belong.
你喜欢男人
You like boys.
可能我喜欢女人
Maybe I like girls.
没有鸡巴盯着你
No penis is staring at you,
盘算如何在你里面喷发
hoping to explode like sticky volcano.
美国  是个可以自由选择的地方  对吧
America-- it's land of choices, yes?
有做我的自由
Freedom to be me.
有做你的自由
Freedom to be you.
麦当劳跟汉堡王在一条街上
Mcdonald's, Burger King on same block.
任你随便选  选一个  选两个都可以
You choose. One, both.
可能我们就去温蒂餐厅了
Shit, maybe we go to Wendy's instead.
等等  你是女同性恋
Hold--you're a lesbian?
可能是  可能不是
Maybe yes, maybe no.
全看自己的选择
Choice.
早上好
Morning.
拖船店的妮卡
Nika from tug shop.
她想让我跟她
She wants to take care of me.
那个死鱼眼的金发女
The blonde with the lazy eye?
她吹小号
She plays trumpet.
舌头很有力
Strong tongue.
但是孩子没得选
But baby no choose.
孩子是我的  也是你的
Baby is me and baby is you.
不能投票  不能来美国那一套
He has no vote, no America.
我们必须照顾他
We must take care of him.
不能只有我一个人
Not just me.
要不然我等你睡着了
Otherwise I wait until you sleep,
我就用螺丝刀子捅你跟那个红毛小子的心脏
and I stab you and orange boy in the heart
然后我就看着你们
with screwdrivers, and I watch you
直到你们血流干而死
bleed until you die.
孩子的事不许再扯皮
No more bullshit about baby.
你也要帮忙
You help.
还有  妮卡要来这住
And Nika comes here to live.
数到三  大家喊杰罗尼莫  准备好了吗
On three, let's say Geronimo. Ready?
美国印第安人阿柏切族首领
莎拉  亲弗兰克爸爸一下
And Sarah, give daddy Frank a kiss.
一  二  三
Oh. One, two, three.
杰罗尼莫
Geronimo.
好了
Got it.
部落会议也许会要照片
Oh, this will be good 'cause
这个可能会派上大用场
the tribal council might want a picture.
看看吧
Let's see.
-怎么了  -你没死
- What? - You're not dead.
你失望了
You disappointed?
你鸡鸡上有个管子
You have a tube in your penis.
-一边去  -还有块大尿片
- Go away. - And a big diaper.
恰奇  别烦你外公
Oh, Chuck, leave your pop-pops alone.
外公
Pop-pops?
-你是我们爸爸了吗  -不是
- Are you our daddy now? - No.
现在不是  不过快了
Not yet, but soon.
就剩一些法律程序
Just a few more legal technicalities.
我们得走完所有流程
We've got to dot some "I"s and cross some "T"s.
你在尿片上拉便便了
Got a big poo in your diaper?
真像是家庭聚会啊
Oh, well, well, this looks like a convention in here.
有这么有爱的一大家子
Aren't you the lucky one to have such a big,
还不够幸运的吗
loving family?
好了  起床了
Okay, up we go.
-早晨得去散散步  -散步
- Time for your morning walk. - A walk?
好的  太好了
Oh, okay. All right.
感觉有点疼
Uh, that sounds a little painful.
能吃点什么东西止痛吗
Can I get a little something extra for that?
起来了
Up we go.
-好的  -没事吧  亲爱的
- Okay. - Ohh, are you okay, dear?
止痛片也不行吗
Ah, come on, not even a percocet?
来几片奥施康定
A couple of oxys?
给我点吧  老天
Something. Jesus!
一步一步慢慢走
One foot in front of the other.
我们今天争取走到礼品店
Let's try and make it all the way down to the gift shop today.
他尿片里有便便
He's got a load in that diaper.
恰奇  对你外公尊重点
Chuck, show your pop-pop some respect.
请不要教训我的孩子
Please don't correct my child.
对不起  总得有人训训他
Well, I'm sorry. Somebody has to.
便便要顺着他的腿流下来了
Poo's gonna run down his leg.
恰奇  别说了  看电视去
Chuckie, knock it off. Watch TV.
我不喜欢你的语气
I don't appreciate your tone.
好吧  你也知道
Oh, well, um, you know,
他现在也是我的外孙了
he's my grandson now too,
所以我也有一定的责任
so I've got to take some responsibility.
他不是你外孙
He's not your grandson.
他是你的那什么  算是继外孙吧
He's your what, step-half-grandson maybe?
而且一小时前爸爸才知道
And dad didn't even know you were married
-你俩结婚了  -这样吧
- until an hour ago. - Let's see.
我们去外边谈  别影响到孩子
How about if we talk outside so we don't bother the kids?
-好的  -我们出去下
- Okay. - We'll be right back.
两个月前他都不知道有你这个人
Two months ago, he didn't know you existed.
他知道的
He knew I existed.
但是他不在乎
And he didn't care.
我不是故意说话难听
I-I don't mean to be cruel.
可是我觉得你们是时候
But I think it's time for you
该考虑下自己的生活了
to start thinking about your own life.
-比如在哪住  -请让一下
- Like, where are you gonna live? - Guys, watch out, please.
等等  什么
What? Wait. What?
你们一直住我的
You've been living at my house,
吃我的  还卖我的家具
eating my food, and selling my furniture.
我们这个新家成立后
With our new family, there just
旅馆的房间不够的
isn't enough room at the inn.
你要赶我们走
You're throwing us out?
今晚我们所有人
Well, we're going, all of us,
都去保留地的领养听证会
to the adoption hearing at the reservation tonight.
我希望回来的时候
And when we come back, I would appreciate it
你们能从我家搬出去
if you were no longer living at my house.
并且我原谅你卖我的家具
And I forgive you for selling the furniture.
妈的
Shit!
靠
Fuck!
怎么了
What?
-现在吗  -是
- Now? - Yep.
我什么都没吃
I haven't taken anything.
门别关
Leave it open.
你没惹麻烦吧
You staying out of trouble?
没有
Yes.
你去戒毒互助会了吗
And you going to your N.A. meetings?
我没有上瘾
I'm not a drug addict.
-我问的不是这个  -去了
- That's not what I asked. - Yes.
你没吸毒
And you're clean?
是的
Yes.
那么我不会在这杯子里找到
So I'm not gonna find nothing in that cup
让我不高兴的东西了
that makes me unhappy?
不会
Nope.
那我们找找看
Let's find out.
哥们  都中午了
Hey, man. It's noon.
太阳都照屁股了  灰姑娘
Rise and fucking shine, Cinderella.
我准备去汤米家买热狗
I'm heading to Tommy's to get a dog.
曼迪说她会照看一会孩子
Mandy said she'd watch the baby meat for a while.
嘿  瞌睡虫
Yo, sleepy-face.
醒醒  哥们  该起床了
Get your ass up, man. Time to roll.
哼哼什么呢
What's that, mumbles?
快点  起床
Come on, get up.
我付钱
I'm buying.
没事吧你
Hey, you okay?
不舒服还是怎么了
Feeling sick or something?
别烦我
Leave me alone.
好吧  要让我给你带点什么吃吗
All right, you want me to bring you back something to eat?
算你厉害  自己玩蛋去吧
All right, man, go fuck yourself.
今天别起来  看我管不管
Sleep all day, see if I care.
他没事吧
He okay?
谁他妈知道
Who the fuck knows?
你真是个怪人
You're a freak.
是真的
It's true.
很厉害的
It has powers.
胡扯
Bullshit.
那就在你脖子上挂条脐带
Hanging an umbilical cord around your neck?
两条脐带
Two umbilical cords.
双胞胎  力量翻倍
Twins--twice the strength.
-没有味道吗  -有
- Doesn't it smell? - Yes.
是有点味道
Well, it kind of smells.
好孩子
Oh, my babies.
还有你们
And you too.
怎么样  米奇
How you doing, Mickey?
楼上生意怎么样
How's business upstairs?
不怎么样
It's slow.
天气太冷了
You know, it's-- it's cold out.
下边生意怎么样  米克
How's business downstairs, Mick?
基佬笑话吗
That a fuckin' gay joke?
不知道  好笑吗
I don't know. Was it funny?
不好笑
No, it wasn't funny.
那就不是基佬笑话
Then, no, it wasn't a gay joke.
嘿  如果有人想叨逼什么
Hey, if anybody's got something to say,
尽管说出来好了
fucking say it!
你很惊讶吗
Were you surprised?
我一点都不觉得惊讶
'Cause I wasn't surprised.
比如洛克·哈德森
I mean, Rock Hudson?
奥斯卡提名男演员  男同  患艾滋死亡
在当年确实令人震惊
That was a bit of a shock.
艾伦
Ellen?
以及《天才小医生》里的那个演员
That kid from Doogie Howser, M.D.?
即尼尔·帕特里克·哈里斯
热播剧《老爸老妈浪漫史》中的巴尼扮演者
艾伦  真的吗  我被骗到了
Ellen? Really? I had that one.
是啊  没有哪个直女会穿阿迪达斯的衣服
Yeah, no straight woman wears Adidas.
罗茜·奥唐纳  倒是骗到我了
Rosie O'Donnell, that got me.
她看上去就跟我妹妹一样
She looks just like my sister.
我以为你妹妹是女同呢
I thought your sister was gay.
在艾伦出柜前她也是直的
Wasn't before Ellen.
埃尔顿·约翰  《风中的蜡烛》
Elton John- candle in the wind.
拍跳水内裤广告的那家伙
That diver from the underwear ads?
马克·沃尔伯格吗
Marky Mark?
马克·沃尔伯格不是同性恋
Marky Mark's not gay.
但他拍了内裤广告啊
He did underwear ads.
不  不  格雷格·洛加尼斯
No, no. Greg Louganis.
没错  他的头撞在了奥运会的跳水板上
Yeah, he busted his head on the olympic diving board.
到处都是血  继续上阵
Blood everywhere, kept going.
真强悍
Tough fucker.
以及去年出柜的那个NBA球员
That NBA player last year.
是啊  杰森·科林斯  真够有勇气的
Yeah, Jason Collins. That took guts.
以及大学生橄榄球联盟中的那个出柜的孩子
What about that kid that just came out in college football,
是叫迈克尔·山姆吧
Michael Sam?
菲姬
Fergie.
菲姬是当红团体黑眼豆豆的女主唱
不是吧  菲姬也是吗
No shit. Fergie?
可能只是双性恋吧  不过也算啦
Well, maybe just bisexual, but still.
米奇  请坐吧  老兄
Mickey, have a seat, man.
没人在乎你干的人是男是女
No one gives a shit who you bang.
我请你喝一杯吧
Let me buy you a beer.
敬基友们
To butt buddies,
祝"花"开永久  "啪"声依旧
long may they slam and slap.
敬基友们
To butt buddies.
还有谁
Who else?
换得怎么样了
How's it going in there?
利普
Lip?
什么事
Yeah?
快出来吧  让我看看
Come on out. Let me see.
肩膀和翻领
Uh, shoulders and lapels.
你对这些翻领满意吗
Are we happy with these lapels?
是阿玛尼牌的吗
Is this the Armani?
保罗·史密斯牌的
Paul Smith.
我们试下普拉达牌的吧
Let's try the Prada.
好吧
Okay.
-别畏畏缩缩的  -老天啊我操
- Stop fidgeting. - Jesus christ.
你可以穿好几年
You'll wear it for years.
我感觉像是  麻雀变凤凰一样
I feel a bit like, uh, Pretty Woman.
鲤鱼跳龙门
Pretty boy.
吃软饭的
Kept boy.
不如叫男宠吧
Boy toy, then.
那个叫法好听点吗
What, that's better?
我要让姐妹会的所有贱人们都羡慕嫉妒恨
I want all those bitches at the sorority suicidal with envy.
原来你大费周章就是那个目的
Oh, that's what this is about.
有何不可
Why not?
在这个世界上
Is there anything on earth
有什么比羞辱同龄人更让人兴奋呢
more enjoyable than humiliating your peers?
走
Go,
去吧
go.
好吧
Okay.
美臀
Yummy.
跟我走
Let's go.
约翰逊女士去哪儿了
Where's Ms. Johnson?
你跟着我就行了
You're with me.
我没吃那颗药  贱人
I didn't take it, bitch.
我没嗑药
I haven't done any drugs.
听着  如果检测结果显示为阳性
Okay, if something showed up in that test,
那一定是检测本身有问题
then there was something wrong with the test,
或者是有人在我的食物或饮料里下了药
or somebody put something in my food or something.
这里有个女人
There's a woman here.
她一直想找我麻烦
She's been giving me a lot of shit.
去拿上你的东西  你可以出去了
Get your stuff. You're out.
上车
Get in the car.
真冷啊
Cold out here.
系上安全带
Seat belt.
饿吗
Hungry?
高速路旁有个便利店
There's a sonic off the highway.
我们到时候停下买点东西给你吃
We'll stop and get you something.
我们已经把气囊里的气都放掉了
We have deflated the balloon,
现在可以拆除尿道中插着的导尿管了
and we are now ready to remove the catheter from the urethra.
恰奇  别看
Chuckie, come on.
你待会儿可能会觉得有点不适
You might feel some discomfort
因为气囊会从你的"管道"中抽出来
as the balloon passes through the meatus.
"管道"
"The meatus."
他说的是我的鸡巴吧
I think he means my dick.
深深地呼一口气
Give me a big exhale.
你通常难道不会让病人...
Don't you normally knock people--
都完成了
All done.
现在开始拆缝合钉吧
Now, let's get those staples out.
侧身躺着
Turn on your side.
恰奇  不要
Chuckie, no.
我们已经让你服用了抑制免疫力之的新山地明
We've started you on a course of immunosuppressive neoral,
你的后半辈子都离不开这个药了
which you'll need to continue for the rest of your life,
来避免出现肝脏移植后的排斥反应
to avoid rejecting your transplant.
该药物有一些副作用
There are a few side effects.
比如高血压  手抖
High blood pressure, hand tremors,
头痛  毛发增多
headaches, increased hair growth,
牙龈肿痛  盗汗
swollen gums, night sweats,
患上抑郁症的可能也大大增加
And an elevated chance of depression.
你还需要服用强的松
You'll also be on prednisone.
那会不会也有科学怪人般的各种副作用
Does that have a Dr. Frankenstein list of side effects, too?
胃溃疡  粉刺  白内障
Stomach ulcers, acne, cataracts,
青光眼  腹泻  噩梦
glaucoma, diarrhea, nightmares,
不眠症  并且毛发生长会更旺盛
insomnia, more hair growth.
能不能开点什么药让我好受一点
What about a little something to take the edge off?
比如止疼药什么的
What about pain meds?
扑热息痛可以减轻你的不适
Tylenol works well for discomfort.
你现在受到感染的几率会很高
You are at increased danger of infection,
所以记得常洗澡  勤洗手
So bathe regularly and wash your hands.
我什么时候可以重新开喝
When can I drink?
酒吗  你再也不能喝了
Alcohol? You can't.
什么
What?
酒精会让肝脏负担过重
Alcohol stresses the liver
并减弱你服用的抗排斥药物的药性
and can dilute your anti-rejection meds.
要是这破肝没法做好本职工作
Well, what's the point of getting a new liver
那换个新肝又有什么意义
if the damn thing won't do what it's designed to do?
试试淡啤吧
Try near beer.
味道出乎意料的好
It's surprisingly tasty,
好几百万前酒鬼都爱上了喝这个
and enjoyed by millions of retired alcoholics,
包括我自己
me included.
他可没说不能抽大麻
He didn't say anything about pot.
我去开
I'll get it.
你点披萨了吗
Did you order a pizza?
超大的芝士干酪  配希腊金椒吗
Extra large, cheesy crust with pepperoncini?
是的
Uh, yeah.
那就是这儿了
This must be the place then.
好的
Okay.
吃饭了
Food!
多少钱
How much?
16块5
Uh, $16.50.
给你20块
Here's 20.
不用找了
Keep the change.
我去拿外套  我们马上走
I'll get my coat, and we can go.
走去哪
Oh. Uh, go?
我在工作呢
I'm--I'm kind of working.
我知道
I know.
我需要你载我去瑟马克大道兑现支票
I need a ride to the check-cashing place on Cermak
再去趟67号街的煤气公司
and the gas company on 67th.
披萨来了
Pizza's here.
我大概一个小时后回来
I'll be back in an hour or so.
我得去付点账单
I have to go pay some bills.
现在在这儿真好
It's nice in here now.
终于不用在屋里也穿皮大衣了
I don't have to wear my parka inside anymore.
黛比说我们可以开暖气
Debbie said we could turn up the heat.
用我给你拿点披萨吗
Want me to get us some pizza?
我不饿
I'm not hungry.
今天全校开大会太搞笑了
That was funny at assembly today
特别是那小妞吐的时候
when that chick threw up.
是啊
Yeah.
有的熊孩子就是撑不住
Some kids just can't hold their jager.
有你妈妈的信儿了吗
You hear anything from your mom?
她会回来的
She'll be back.
她最多也就会离开大概  一两晚吧
She never stays away for more than, like, a night or two.
还想在这里过夜吗
Want to spend the night here again?
你哥不是说不想看到我们在这儿吗
I thought your brother said he didn't want us around.
这也是我的家
It's my house too.
我有点东西要给你
I got you something.
你给我买的吗
You bought me that?
偷的  但这不重要
Stole, but yeah.
你不会开始喜欢我了吧
You're not starting to like me or anything, are you?
喜欢你
Like you?
比如  爱上我什么的
Like, fall in love or anything weird?
没有
No.
那就好  最好别
Good, don't.
为什么
Why not?
反正就是不要
Just don't.
我回车上去了
I should get back to the van,
万一我妈回来了呢
in case mom shows up.
谢谢你的啤酒
Thanks for the beer.
来吧  孩子们
Come on, guys.
该走了
Time to go.
该走了  走吧
Time to go. Let's go.
你知道为什么放你出来吗
You know why you out?
不知道  但是谢谢你
No, but thank you.
别谢我
Yeah, don't thank me.
跟我没关系
It wasn't me.
里面人满为患
Overcrowding.
非暴力罪犯在服刑10%到20%的时间后
Non-violent offenders rotate out
都会轮换出狱
after 10% to 20% time served.
你为什么又跑去嗑药狂欢
So what sent you on that bender,
违反了缓刑条例
made you bust your probation?
我不知道
I don't know.
也许就是人生太艰难了
Maybe it just got too hard.
你有点太轻松放纵自己了  不是吗
Letting yourself off a little easy, don't you think?
我又回到了监狱
I went back to jail.
那可一点都不轻松
There's nothing easy about that.
当然了
Sure it is.
最难的地方就是洁身自好  不再复吸
The hard part is staying out and clean.
旧病复发是很容易的
Relapsing is easy.
我不是瘾君子
I'm not a drug addict.
是啊  你一直这么说
Yeah, so you keep saying.
这是事实
It's the truth.
那你后来到底是怎么回事
Then what was all that about then, huh?
我真的不知道
I honestly don't know.
那你的悲惨经历是什么
Then what's your sad story?
因为我们都会以不同的方式搞砸人生
'cause we all screwed up in one way or the other.
我们那里可没有多少高档的白篱笆围栏
Not many white picket fences where we come from.
你也是南部贫困区的人
You're south side?
土生土长
Born and raised.
我爸爸酗酒
My dad drank.
我爱他  但他是个酒鬼
I loved him, but he was a drunk.
但你是个成年人
But you a grown-up.
人生当中会遇到一个点
There comes a point in time that
让你自己掌握自己的生活
you got to take control of your own life.
不论出身如何  不论谁辜负了你
Whatever you from, whoever did you wrong,
没有尽到他们的本职责任
didn't do what they were supposed to do,
没有成为他们应该成为的样子
wasn't being who they was supposed to be?
一切该取决于你
It's just you.
没有借口
No more excuses.
哟  都5点多了
Yo, it's after 5:00.
你是想创个什么记录吗
You trying to set some sort of record?
别睡了  起来
You're not still sleeping. Get up.
别烦我
Leave me alone.
伊恩  你嗑药了吗
Ian, are you high?
你服用什么了吗
You take something?
滚开
Go away.
至少让我给俱乐部打个电话  告诉他们
Okay, you want me to call the club at least and tell them--
上帝  离我远点
Jesus! Leave me alone!
这他妈怎么了
Fuck's wrong with him?
总之
And in conclusion,
我认为我同我的丈夫可以提供一个温暖
I feel my husband and I can provide a warm,
包容  有教养的生活环境
inclusive, nurturing environment
更有效地推进我们共有的
that validates the cultural identity
对于印第安文化的认同
of our shared Native American heritage.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你  加拉格夫人
Thank you, Mrs. Gallagher.
我相信我这么说可以代表所有人
I'm sure I speak for all of us
我们很感激你表现出的
when I say we appreciate the diligence
对这些孩子们无微不至的关心
you have shown in caring for these children.
我代表我们之中的大多数
Well, then, I speak for most of us
表示你的奉献令人印象深刻
when I say your devotion is very impressive.
加里  他们在说什么
Gary, what are they saying?
我不知道
I don't know.
我选的是中文
I'm taking Chinese.
我很愿意回答  不好意思
I'd be--I'd be happy to answer--I'm sorry.
不是故意打断你们
I didn't mean to interrupt.
如果我可以回答任何问题...
But if I can answer any questions--
谢谢  请给我们一点时间
Thank you, but give us a moment.
好吧
Okay.
不行
No.
什么不行
No what?
你不能领养这些孩子
You cannot adopt the children.
他们的祖父会抚养他们
Their grandfather will take them.
祖父
Grandfather?
曾祖父
Great-grandfather.
你怎么不说你们还有祖父
Why didn't you tell me you had a grandfather?
他家里没有无线网
He doesn't have wi-fi.
默诺默尼族谢谢你
The menominee nation thanks you for
照顾这些孩子
your care Of these children
我们想给你500元
and would like to offer you $500
补偿您可能支付的任何开支
to defray any costs you may have incurred.
我们可以寄支票给你
We can send you a check.
还是你想换成赌场的筹码
Or would you prefer chips for the casino?
脚踝抬起来
Give me your ankle.
上次那个弄丢了欠我420块
You owe me 420 bucks for the last one.
快来
Come on, let's go.
你上班要迟到了
You're gonna be late for work.
你也是盖尔负责的令她头痛的犯人  是吧
So, you're another one of Gayle's hard cases, huh?
我叫查理·彼得斯
Charlie Peters.
最低工资加小费
Minimum wage plus tips.
生意好的话  你一小时能赚12块
Good shift, you'll bring home 12 bucks an hour.
生意差点  大概有8块吧
If it rains or snows, closer to 8.
做过侍应生吗
You wait tables before?
基本是鸡尾酒那种
Uh, cocktails mostly.
醉酒来上班  我就炒了你
You come in drunk, you're fired.
嗑药来上班  我也炒了你
You come in high, you're fired
还要打电话给约翰逊女士
And I call ms. Johnson here.
明白了吗
We clear?
加入什么互助会了吗
You got a meeting?
还没
Not yet.
戒毒还是戒酒
N.A. Or a.A.?
戒毒
N.A.
戒酒也要吧
Al-anon too, I'm guessing.
我在街尾圣公会有个互助会
I got a meeting down the street at the episcopal.
早上十点
10:00 a.M.
杰姬
Jackie.
杰姬·斯科瓦洛  菲奥娜·加拉格
Jackie scavello, Fiona Gallagher.
你带她去里间
You take her in the back,
安排一个柜子给她
set her up with a locker,
跟她说说规矩
Show her the ropes.
好
Sure.
谢谢
Thanks.
这个能撑下来吗
This one gonna make it?
谁知道呢
Who knows?
萨咪来电话了
Sammi called.
弗兰克明天出院
Frank's getting out of the hospital tomorrow.
我们应该过去
We should go.
你女朋友呢
Where's your girlfriend?
不知道
I don't know.
她不接我电话
She's not answering my calls.
你男朋友呢
Where's your boyfriend?
在上班
Working.
他现在不是我男朋友
And he's not my boyfriend now.
要等我16岁
He's my friend until I'm 16,
可以合法性交了才是
And we can legally have consensual intercourse.
悲剧
Sucks.
是啊
Mm-hmm, yeah.
你哥在吗
Your brother here?
他不是住在你家呢吗
I thought he was staying with you.
不是  老弟
No, come on, man.
你另一个哥哥  利普
The other one. The--the--lip.
在大学
College.
出什么事了吗
Something wrong?
*天堂众神*
*Gods of the heaven*
*以血为契*
*Bound with blood forever*
*兄弟姐妹*
*Sisters and brothers*
*团结一致*
*We are bound together*
*天堂众神*
*Gods of the heaven*
*以血为契*
*Bound with blood forever*
*兄弟姐妹*
*Sisters and brothers*
你看过恐怖片《罗斯玛丽的婴儿》吗
Have you ever seen rosemary's baby?
*团结一致*
*We are bound together*
*天堂众神*
*Gods of the heaven*
*以血为契*
*Bound with blood forever*
*兄弟姐妹*
*Sisters and brothers*
*团结一致*
*We are bound together*
*天堂众神*
*Gods of the heaven*
*以血为契*
*Bound with blood forever*
唱得真好
You sounded amazing.
滚开
伊恩
Ian?
伊恩  你还好吗
Ian, you all right?
伊恩  我是黛比
Ian, it--it's Debbie.
走开
Go away.
伊恩
Ian?
知道这是什么情况吗
Do you know what this is?
是的  我们知道
Yeah, we know what this is.
也没有很糟吧
That wasn't so bad, was it?
诵唱那部分是有点诡异
Uh, no, the chanting part was kind of creepy.
不过我穿西服很帅嘛
But hey, I look good in a suit, right?
我以为是更狂野的长袍派对
You know, I figured it was gonna be more
而不是女巫集会
Wild toga party than coven.
我们都是工程系的
Well, we're a bunch of engineering majors.
我们的派对通常就是
Our parties usually consist of us
看《生活大爆炸》重播
Watching big bang reruns
互相漂白胡须
And bleaching each other's mustaches.
-大家都要咖啡吗  -要
- Everybody want coffee? - Oh, yes, please.
好的
Okay, great.
学步屋早餐有特价
We've got a special on the toddle house breakfast.
是火腿芝士煎蛋卷
It's a ham and cheese omelet.
有香肠或培根  粗燕麦粉
It's got sausage or bacon, grits--
粗燕麦粉  或者可以选吐司
Grits, um, with a choice of toast,
只要4.99元
And it's 4.99.
我过会儿来帮你们点单
Okay, I'll be back to take your order.
不好意思  我去上个厕所
Excuse me, I just got to go take a leak.
曼迪
Mandy, hey.
你还要咖啡吗  先生
You want some more coffee, sir?
不  不用
Uh, no, no.
我不知道你在这里上班
Um, hey, look. I didn't know you worked here.
我马上就会过去为您服务
I'll be with your table in just a minute.
你气色不错
You look great.
你要点别的吗
You want something else?
加糖吗
More sugar?
或者奶油
Cream?
不用了
No, uh...
不用加了
No, we're good.
谢谢
Thank you.
你认识那个服务员吗
You know the waitress?
我以为是以前学校里的同学
Oh, I thought I did from school.
你们看见凯伦晚上穿的那条裙子了吗
Did you guys see Karen's dress tonight?
你们想吃点什么
So what are you guys thinking, huh?
大份蛋饼怎么样
How about the mega-omelet?
好啊
Yeah.
菲奥娜
Fiona.
我在做法式土司
I'm making french toast.
天呐
Oh, Jesus.
你哭了吗
Are you crying?
别哭了  我也要哭了
Oh, don't cry. I'll start crying too.
好啦  好啦
Okay, okay, enough.
别哭啦
Jesus, stop.
去上学吧
School, come on.
你们得动作快点
We've got to get moving.
怎么了
What?
老天  出什么事了
God, what?
想起床了吗
You want to get up?
我做三明治给你吃
I'll make you a sandwich.
要不我去把跑鞋换上
Or I could get my sneakers in the house.
我们出去跑步吧
We could go for a run at the track.
你想跑跑步
You want to go for a run?
呼吸点新鲜空气吗
Get some fresh air?
你觉得如何
What do you say?
好的  好的
Okay, okay.
他这样多久了
How long has he been like that?
昨天早上就开始了
Since yesterday morning.
到现在没起过床吗
And he hasn't gotten out of bed?
没  他就一直睡着
No, he's just sleeping.
我叫过他几次  他就是不起来
I can't get him up. I-I tried.
是啊  我也叫了
Yeah, so did I.
之前呢  他什么样子
And what about before? What was he like?
之前他很好  兴高采烈的
Before, he was fine. He was happy.
他整宿不睡
He's staying up all hours of the night,
又跳舞  又说笑话
dancing, telling fucking jokes.
他每天都要折腾我  我根本跟不上他的节奏
He kicks my ass every day. I can't keep up with him.
我们得联系利普
We've got to get ahold of Lip.
得告诉他
He should know.
告诉什么  他怎么了
Know what? What's wrong with him?
我觉得  是抑郁
Uh, depression, I think.
他抑郁了
He--he's depressed?
什么叫他...  我们都他妈抑郁
What do you mean he's-- we all get fucking depressed.
住在这种地方  怎么可能不抑郁
How the fuck could we not, living around here?
不是你想的那种抑郁
It's not that kind of depressed, okay?
听着  可能是我想错了
Look, I could be wrong,
但伊恩可能得了躁郁症  就跟我们妈妈一样
But it could be bipolar disease, like our mom.
躁郁什么  什么玩意
Bi--bi--bi-what? What the fuck is that?
就是狂躁型抑郁症  米奇
It's manic depression, Mick.
就好像先嗨到爆  然后跌到底
It's like high highs followed by low lows,
不断循环
over and over again.
我们得带他去诊所看病
We'll get him an appointment at the clinic,
看看医生怎么说
And we'll see what they say.
不  他只是情绪低落
No, no, look. He--he's low.
-我们逗他开心就好了  -不是这样的
- We cheer him up. - It's not like that.
他可能需要住院治疗
He may have to be hospitalized.
什么住院  精神病院那样的吗
What do you mean, hos-- like a psych ward?
休想  休想
No fucking way! No fucking way!
他就待在这儿
He's staying here.
他可能会自杀的
He could end up suicidal.
那他好转前  我们就把刀藏起来
Then we hide the knives until he perks up.
我...  我能照顾他
I can--I can take care of him.
他好转前  就由我来照顾
Okay, let me take care of him until he's better.
这可能要几周
It--it can be weeks.
他的情绪会忽好忽坏
It's mood swings, okay?
你搞不定的
It's almost impossible to handle.
别他妈说什么搞不定
Don't fucking tell me what's impossible!
我们就在这照顾他
We're taking care of him here.
你  我  我们
You, me, us.
他是我们的家人
He's fucking family.
我还得去互助会
I have to get to a meeting, okay?
待会儿给利普打电话
Um, we'll call Lip,
告诉他现在的情况
And we'll let him know what's going on.
好吗  走吧
Okay, come on.
他不会去精神病院的
He's not going to some fucking nut house.
你听见了吗
You hear me?
他就留在这
He stays here.
他必须跟我待在一起
He's staying with me.
昨天有辆货车停在这里
You see a van parked here,
车上还住着很多小孩
bunch of kids living in it?
你见过吗
It was here yesterday.
是啊  昨天是在
Yeah. Yeah, they were here.
估计开走了吧
Must have left.
很高兴见到你
Good to see you.
互助会要开始了
The meeting's about to start.
你先请
After you.
早上好
Good morning.
让一下
Uh, excuse me?
你今天不能进加拉格先生的病房
You're not allowed in Mr. Gallagher's room today.
什么
What?
加拉格太太要求
Mrs. Gallagher has requested that
不让你进病房
You not be allowed in the room.
他是我爸爸
He's my dad.
她觉得你在场
She's concerned that your presence
会让加拉格先生动怒
is upsetting to mr. Gallagher.
希拉
Sheila!
希拉  滚出来
Sheila, get your fat ass out here!
抱歉  我不想叫保安
Please, I don't want to have to call security.
老娘要给你好看
I'm just gonna-- - I'm gonna fuck you up!
-叫保安  -你惹毛我了
- Call security. - You fuck with the bull,
你死定了
You get an ass full of horns!
小声点
Keep your voice down.
你不能不让我见我爸爸
You can't keep me away from my dad.
他是我丈夫
He is my husband.
-我是她的骨肉  -我是他老婆
- I'm his blood. - I'm his wife.
你还有孩子  而他是我唯一的亲人了
You've got your kids. He's the only family I've got.
不  孩子没了
No, I lost the kids.
部落不肯让我领养他们
The tribe wouldn't let me adopt them.
太遗憾了
Oh, I'm so sorry.
以后你家就有地方给我们住了
So now you have room for us at your house.
让我见我爸  贱人
Let me see my father, you bitch.
不行
No!
我是他选择要相伴一生的人
I'm the one he's chosen to spend the rest of his life with.
你只是个运气好的精子而已
You're just one lucky sperm.
她说我不能见我亲爹
She says I can't see my dad!
加拉格夫人
Mrs. Gallagher.
我非常抱歉...
I am so sorry to--
她刚刚袭击了我
She just assaulted me!
是她袭击了我
I was assaulted!
外面闹什么呢
What's going on out there?
女人打仗  萨咪和希拉
Catfight-- Sammi and Sheila.
为什么打仗
Over what?
好像是为了你
You, I think.
谁赢了
Who's winning?
难说
Hard to tell.
可能是保安吧
Maybe the rent-a-cops.
准备好离开这里了吗
You ready to get out of here?
等不及
Absolutely.
女士们  请你们小声一点
Ladies, I need you to keep it down.
这里是美国  在这个国家
This is America, and in this country,
人们有权利见自己的家人
people have a right to see their families.
拜拜
Bye.
没事了
It's fine.
我们自己会处理好的
Okay, we're gonna work it out.
我先去见我爸爸了
I'm just gonna go and see my dad.
不  我靠
Oh, no, god damn it.
爸爸
Dad?
Pops?
你对尼古丁的热忱真是令人敬佩
Your dedication to nicotine is admirable.
现在气温几度  五度吗
What is it, five degrees?
至少有十度吧
It's at least ten.
得躁郁症了吗
Bipolar, huh?
还不确定
Can't be sure.
但那场景看起来心疼地熟悉
But it looked painfully familiar.
莫妮卡的锂药片可能还在
We should have some of Monica's lithium somewhere.
反正她从来也不吃
It's not like she ever took it.
我还一直担心会是我
And I always worried it'd be me.
还有时间呢
Oh, there's still time.
我听说  躁郁症初次发作
You know, I hear you could have your first
会是在人的少年时期或者二十出头的时候
psychotic break anytime in your teens or 20s.
精神病的俄罗斯转盘游戏
Mental illness Russian Roulette
莫妮卡的基因是子弹
with Monica's DNA as the bullet.
酗酒是基因遗传的吗
Is alcoholism genetic?
不是  是环境因素造成的
It's the nurture part of nature and nurture.
主要是人的成长环境起的作用
All about the environment you grow up in.
那还真是振奋人心
Oh, that's very encouraging.
老天
Jesus.
这个家什么时候才能脱离霉运
Is this family ever gonna catch a break?
你出狱了
Well, you're out of the pokey,
我...也通过了期中考试
and, uh, I passed my midterms.
太棒了  真有你的
That's great, good for you.
刚刚过及格线
Barely, but I passed.
我打赌你成绩好极了
I bet you aced 'em.
大学可比看起来的苦逼多了
College is a lot fucking harder than it looks.
真得专心致志的学
You actually have to apply yourself.
阿曼达是什么角色
Who exactly is Amanda?
我室友的前女友
My, uh, roommate's ex-girlfriend,
趁我睡着了给我吹箫
who I ended up with when she tried
然后我俩就在一起了
to blow me in my sleep.
你睡着了别人还可以给你吹箫吗
Somebody can blow you in your sleep?
吹到某个时刻  你就醒了
Well, at some point, you wake up.
开始认真了吗
Is it getting serious?
开始古怪了倒是真的
Well, it's certainly getting fucking weird.
她给我买东西
She buys me shit.
-高档货吗  -是
- Nice shit? - Yeah.
那你可得抓牢
Sounds like a keeper.
是我  利普
It was me, Lip.
不是弗兰克
Not Frank.
不是莫妮卡
Not Monica.
不是基因  不是环境
Not nature. Not nurture.
是我自己的错
It was all me.
我23岁了
I'm 23.
跟父母有多糟糕已经没有关系了
It can't be about how much they screwed us up anymore.
像是互助会听到的自白
It sounds kind of like AA.
是啊
Yeah.
你已经被那些互助会洗脑了吗
You been drinking the big book kool-aid?
有一点  假释条例规定一定要出席
A bit. Attendance is a condition of my parole.
你不是完人  菲奥娜
You're not perfect, Fiona.
我们都不是
None of us are.
挺好  乔治  谢谢啦
Looks good, George. Thanks.
恰奇  拿着水管
Hey, Chuckie, grab the hose.
把水接上  好吗
Hook up our water, okay?
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
安营扎寨
Homesteading.
你要在我院子里安营扎寨
You're camping in my yard?
不是你的院子
Not your yard.
是你院子旁边的空地
The vacant lot next to your yard.
跟市政局投诉去呀
Complain to the city planning department.
夏天的时候  他们应该就会
They should get around to sending somebody
派人来调查了
to investigate by summer.
你见到弗兰克了吗
Have you seen Frank?
他不在这吗
He's not here?
不在  我问了黛比  她也没见到他
No. And I talked to Debbie, and she hasn't seen him either.
我做了炖肉  给弗兰克的
I made a pot roast for Frank.
浪费了好像太可惜
And it seems like a shame to have it go to waste,
你们饿吗
if you guys are hungry.
我们饿  谢谢
We could eat, thanks.
好吧
Okay.
小恰  有炖肉吃
Chuckie, pot roast!
这里行吗
Is this good?
把酒给我
Give me the bottle.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
确定
Absolutely.
你就这点本事吗
That all you got?
没招了吗
That's it?
我还在这  你这混蛋
I'm still here, you fucker!
弗兰克·加拉格
Frank Gallagher!
老子还活着
I'm alive!
你看见老子了吗
You see me?
看见老子站在这了吗
You see me standing here?
你输了  混蛋
You lost, asshole!
老子活着  臭不要脸的
I'm alive, motherfucker!
我  弗兰克·加拉格
Me, Frank Gallagher!
活着
Alive.
喝一小口死不了
Little nip won't hurt you.
你要进去吗
Are you gonna go in?
是这栋楼没错吧
Is this the right house?
杰克
Jack?
你要不要进去
Are you gonna go inside?
不  今晚不进去了
No. Not tonight.
我们走吧
Come on, let's go.